Dylan Salay

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Full stack web developer, backed by 4+ years in Finance/Operations, with proven success managing complex procedures across fast-paced, deadline driven environments. Solid interpersonal skills, capable of building relationships with peers, clients and key decision makers to establish a cohesive work culture. Excited to expand and refine my development skills through my passion for problem solving.

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN

2019 - PRESENT

Notch8 | San Diego, CA

Notch8 is a consultancy firm that specializes in building web and mobile applications for a wide range of clients.

- Currently working with a team of interns and developers on version 3 of REU Manager (www.reumanager.com).
- Addressing tickets delegated via GitLab.
- Utilizing Docker, Ruby on Rails. and RSpec.

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER IN TRAINING

2019

LEARN Academy | San Diego, CA

Full-time, intensive coding boot camp that provides students with hands-on training and the skills necessary to become full stack web developers.

- Experienced 480+ hours of direct coding experience developing web applications.
- Developed a range of fully functioning applications utilizing JavaScript, React, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, HTML and CSS.
- Applied a variety of agile development strategies including pair programming, mob programming and behavior driven development.
- Implemented testing techniques, such as Enzyme, Jest and RSpec, to maintain fully functioning code.
- Used Git/Github to comply with version control best practices.

FINANCIAL/OPERATIONS ANALYST

2015 - 2019

Verus Investments | Seattle, WA

Investment advisory firm focused on providing strategic, tailored investment solutions to institutional clients.

- Utilized Microsoft Excel to build custom finanical models and implement creative solutions to meet client needs.
- Took initiative to oversee process improvements and established a best practices guide for the Analyst role.
- Produced monthly and quarterly investment reports, and custom analytics for clients pitches and meetings.
- Presented financial results to consultants in order to make informed decisions on various investments.
- Upheld the financial integrity of institutional clients by executing trades and cash movements, confirming trade settlements and reconciling positions.

CONTACT

Email: dylansalay@gmail.com

Phone: 928-814-3246

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/dylansalay

Github: github.com/dylansalay

SOFTWARE SKILLS

JavaScript

Ruby

CSS

HTML

Jest

RSpec

React

Ruby on Rails

PostgreSQL

Bootstrap

Git/Github

PERSONAL SKILLS

Problem solving & analysis

Critical thinking

Time management

Collaboration

Attention to detail

Active listening

EDUCATION

Gonzaga University

2010 - 2014

Bachelor of Business Administration

Concentrations:

Finance & Economics

Cum Laude